# MOHAMMAD MATIN

# **AZIMI**

Github.com/matinazimi



# **ABOUT ME**

Three years ago, I took a personality test. It helped me to understand that I had great abilities to be a programmer. From that day on, my interests in this profession increased day by day, until I decided to work professionally in this field.

It's really enjoyable for me to be in a part of a team and use my abilities. Also it is very delightful to encourage your teammates by your perseverance.

I'm a swimming coach and I spend my free time to exercise professionally, because I believe that "when our body is not in the healthy way, our brain wouldn't have it's best function"



#### **EDUCATION**

MBA (Marketing) | Iran University of Science and Technology

1398 - 1400

CIVIL ENGINEERING (Hydraulic resources) | Imam Khomeini International University

1394 - 1398



# **EXPERIENCE**

### **BACK-END DEVELOPER | Ariana Labs (web site)**

SEPTEMBER, 2020 - PRESENT

- We are IRANCELL's operation team and provide services for it.
- Our duty is Service Management Specialist, Ticket Handling, Incident Management.
- Design and develop ticketing APP system base on ITLE service management.

#### **BACK-END DEVELOPER | MPSA**

JUNE, 2020 – SEPTEMBER, 2020

- Designing an online Ticket-selling website. (Group project)
- Designing an Online Store. (Individual Project) (Available in Github: Click Here)
- Both projects were full-Stack and done in DRF.

# BUSINESS STRATEGIST | Tazmin San'at Sobhan Co (web site)

SEPTEMBER, 2019 - NOVEMBER, 2019

- Finding new target customers/Running SWOT & GSPM matrices.



#### **MILITARY**

Exempted



#### **SKILLS**

- Python Programming
- Django
- DRF (Django Rest Framework)
- PostgresSQL

- Git
- Docker
- Nginx
- Linux

- MySQL
- HTML/CSS
- JQuery
- OOP